(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
(After the 4 siblings' memorable 1st dinner together)
- Sun Young.
- Yes?
- Are you tired?
- I'm not tired at all.
- How about a round of omok?
- What?
- Sure.
- You say that you hardly lose.
- I'm really good at it.
It's hard for you to lose, right?
- Are you good at omok?
- Omok? No way.
I'm seriously good at omok.
I don't think I can lose at omok.
He says that he can't lose at omok.
- I'm good at omok.
- If I win, you have to pay me...
- Me too.
- I'm good at omok.
I'm quite good at omok too.
- If I win...
Me too.
Is there a go board here?
There is.
I saw it as soon as I got here.
I see.
(Who will win the match between these self-proclaimed omok masters?)
(The game of omok starts.)
(The two omok masters are taking the game seriously.)
You've got a nice vibe.
This is the most serious I've seen you all day.
(Roh Yoon Seo watching from the sidelines)
I must win.
- Now...
- You're good at it.
I should watch and learn.
- You're actually quite good.
- You too.
(About 30 minutes later)
(Pouting)
(Keeping a poker face behind his sunglasses)
Where did you study?
Here and there.
I studied near Mount Jiri.
- Mount Jiri?
- Yes.
Since I'm from Gangwon Province, I studied at Mount Seorak.
Places like Mount Seorak and Mount Taebaek.
That's some serious training ground.
(Sliding)
(Laughing triumphantly)
What's going on?
(Is it finally over?)
Did you win?
That's incredible.
- Goodness.
- This is four...
(It's a 4-3.)
(Sun Young from Mount Jiri wins.)
Is it because of this?
- Sun Young, you're good.
- You're quite good.
- Let's play once more.
- I've never lost before.
Seriously?
- Let's play 1 more round.
- There are 2 masters on our team.
(Round 2)
I bet I'll lose again.
- Please let me win this time.
- Watch out.
(The game speeds up.)
(Tap)
(You Seok places what he believes is the winning move.)
What? I didn't see that before.
(Pure happiness)
(You Seok from Mount Seorak wins.)
- You did a good job.
- I did well.
I know. I didn't even see it.
It was another 4-3.
You're very good at it now.
This is perfect.
Anyway,
today's score is 1 to 1.
(Moaning)
- Mister.
- The game was enjoyable today.
It had a good impact on you.
- Mount Seorak, I mean.
- It was a good game.
It must be the spirit of Gangwon Province.
- What do you think of the vibe?
- Oh, my.
I changed the atmosphere a little. Isn't it nice?
When you film with this, it looks like we're in an old movie.
- It's rolling.
- Yes.
(Their first night in Tongyeong)
It's rolling.
(Jung Ah and Yoon Seo)
(This time, she puts on a face mask and grabs the microphone.)
(Late-night karaoke begins.)
(Among the crowd)
(To me, you are)
Oh, come on.
(They're playing another game.)
What? That's nonsense.
(Together and apart,)
(the 4 siblings settle into their 1st night together.)
(Wiggling)
There he is. Go on and sing.
- Aren't you going to sing?
- No.
When is the performance? The dance goes like this.
(Being totally cute)
You're a goof ball.
- He's like our baby brother.
- He's a little rascal.
You Seok doesn't act cute with just anyone.
Right?
- He's like a cat.
- He doesn't act cute...
- with just anyone.
- He's a cat.
(His cuteness is reserved for his older siblings.)
You'd better not let me hear you...
acting cute with anyone else.
(The eldest gets strict about his acting cute.)
You hear me?
My goal is to win you all over.
That's what I'd like.
- Like last time?
- By acting cute?
Like when you made us laugh on the boat?
That's just...
- the tip of the iceberg.
- That was...
(Captain Kang was the tip of the iceberg.)
- He was gross.
- It was 1 out of 10.
"Gross?"
- You're being very honest again.
- I don't like men like him.
I hate men like him.
(Laughing)
I will never forget him.
- Let's go to bed.
- Please go ahead.
Aren't you going to bed?
I will after I clean up.
(Wrapping things up with a clean finish)
I'm going out for a walk.
(Not quite ready to call it a night)
(The youngest two head out for a late-night walk.)
Look at the stars.
We can see the stars.
- There are so many.
- We can see the stars.
(The night sky is blanketed with stars.)
That's a constellation.
- Isn't that the Cassiopeia?
- Where?
It's right here. The one that looks like this.
Look over here.
It's the Big Dipper.
- Really?
- It's shaped like a ladle.
You can see the Big Dipper so clearly.
Let's go to the rooftop.
Will we get a better view up there?
(The ocean stretches out in full view even at the rooftop.)
(They capture the moment under the sky overflowing with stars.)
Brush your teeth out here. It feels more special this way.
I feel like I'm at my grandmother's house.
Yes.
We can see the sea from here,
and the weather is perfect.
(Their first night in Tongyeong comes to an end.)
(It's too beautiful to sleep through.)
(The darkness slowly fades.)
(A new day dawns over Tongyeong.)
(The sea is the first to wake.)
(As the harbour comes to life,)
(the fishing village slowly begins another day.)
(What adventures await us today?)
(Current time: 6am)
(Sun Young gets up.)
(Starting the morning with stretching)
(Kicking off the day with a productive morning routine)
(Even with a spacious living room,)
(she still ends up settling in the kitchen.)
(Peeling and enjoying Korean melon for breakfast)
(Savouring a relaxing cup of coffee)
(Did she find something?)
(Eating)
(Sneaking bites of the crew's snacks from the corner of the yard)
(One isn't enough. It's time to raid another snack.)
(The wrapper disappears neatly into her pocket.)
(When Sun Young wakes up early, she eats a lot of snacks.)
(Soon, Jung Ah gets up.)
- Jung Ah.
- What are you...
(Yoon Seo also gets up.)
- Did you sleep well?
- Why did you get up so early?
(Crawling)
You look cute. You're cuter in the morning.
Jung Ah.
What else should I know?
Did you eat some Korean melon this morning?
I had coffee,
and I ate two of the snacks the production crew had hidden.
Snacks?
I raided the crew's snack stash.
- Where did you find it?
- In the flower bed.
You're better than me.
- I didn't even know it existed.
- In the flower bed.
I woke up at 6am.
I had nothing to do.
I was really bored.
- They should've given us books.
- Right.
- There was nothing to do.
- Why didn't you go back to sleep?
(You Seok wakes up.)
Sun Young, do you want to borrow my books?
(He brings out books that he packed.)
Gosh, look at him. I don't believe you.
- Have you read them?
- I've been reading this book.
Really? That's incredible.
- This is unbelievable.
- Then you can read this.
Jung Ah, look at him.
(The two of them have been reading the same book.)
You Seok brought this. Isn't that funny?
You two really seem to click.
(He also feels good.)
(Sun Young gets ready to prepare the ingredients for breakfast.)
All right, shall I start?
I have to keep talking...
to the viewers so there's no awkward silence.
("Kim Sun Young's AM Plaza")
Hello, everyone. From early morning, we're cooking...
delicious food before heading out to earn a living.
Isn't this the dream? In the countryside yard...
What do you call this? A sink.
I can't block the camera. You all have to see it.
(The communication expert turns her back to the camera anyway.)
I'm going to blanch the squid, so a quick...
rinse will do.
(Washing the squid quickly before blanching)
This is...
trash.
(Washing the vegetables)
If I turn up the water,
the camera director will get soaked.
This is how you wash it clean.
It's not bad, right?
That's done.
I'll wash this too.
(When Jung Ah arrives)
Here you go.
Just leave it there. Let me get some water.
We used to wash our hair here and splash water on our necks.
(She can't resist for long.)
All right, like this.
(It's a full-blown water show.)
You need a strong stream of water.
You can rinse it roughly...
when Jung Ah isn't looking.
I'll peel the potatoes, so they can be washed roughly.
- Who are you talking to?
- I'm talking to the viewers.
Stop talking to the viewers and talk to us instead.
I'm washing the vegetables according to Jung Ah's orders.
- Aren't you going to wash these?
- Shall I...
- I washed them all.
- Wash these too.
("Kim Sun Young's AM Plaza" ends abruptly.)
(The preparations continue.)
(What's on the siblings' breakfast menu?)
We're going to make chungmu gimbap.
(Along with fresh seafood)
(A dish that represents Tongyeong)
(Chungmu gimbap)
(When the gimbap fishermen used to take on their boats spoiled fast)
(Radish and cabbage kimchi, squid and fishcake, gimbap)
(It originated from packing the rice and side dishes separately.)
(To go with the siblings' chungmu gimbap)
Chungmu gimbap...
and pollack roe and tofu soup.
It's simple to make. We have to eat fast and go to work.
(A meal that looks simple but not quite comes together.)
(Shall we prepare the ingredients?)
The squid sounds delicious.
It sounds delicious.
The squid will be delicious.
It'll be delicious.
- It's full of protein.
- Oh, my.
(Yoon Seo is in charge of gimbap in chungmu gimbap.)
It's warm.
(Sniffing)
The rice smell.
Gosh, it's hot.
(Even while scooping rice, the endless chatter continues.)
- Jung Ah, do we season the rice?
- Yes, season it with sesame oil.
Just sesame oil?
Season it with sesame oil...
- and a bit of seasoned salt.
- Okay.
This is for the soup.
(Jung Ah sets water to boil for soup...)
(and starts prepping the ingredients.)
(Squid that Sun Young rinsed roughly)
(That's a beautiful mind)
(Cutting it into beautiful, bite-sized pieces)
How much more spring onion shall I cut?
- That's enough for the soup.
- Is it enough?
- And?
- And this.
(The youngest took a seat next to them.)
(Sprinkling)
Sesame oil.
(Pouring sesame oil lightly)
Seasoned salt.
(Sprinkling seasoned salt)
(When you massage it with your hands)
It's hot.
(It's hot.)
(The steam is still rising.)
I should've used this.
(She quickly switches to using a spatula.)
You Seok, let me know when the water starts to boil.
One of them is boiling.
Then could you blanch the fishcake very lightly?
- For ten minutes?
- Let's see...
- No, 30 minutes.
- For 30 minutes.
- Is it okay not to cut it?
- Yes.
And blanch the squid for about 1 to 2 minutes.
Can I blanch them in the same water?
- In the same water.
- Okay.
(You Seok is in charge of fishcake and squid.)
(When the water reaches a gentle boil with fishcake)
(The key is to take it out before it gets too soft.)
- Is it already done?
- Where shall I put it?
- And the squid.
- I'll leave it here.
Okay. Here's the squid.
(Next, it's time to cook the squid.)
(Shake off the squid and toss it in.)
For how long do I blanch the squid?
About 1 to 2 minutes.
(When he's given 1 to 2 minutes,)
(he diligently washes the dishes.)
(The youngest also finished seasoning the rice.)
Jung Ah, what should I do now?
- The rice is ready.
- Wrap it.
- Wrap it?
- Yes.
Do I wrap the rice with dried laver?
I don't know how to make chungmu gimbap.
I see. Cut the dried laver into four pieces.
- Okay.
- Give it a try. I'll show you.
(Cutting is my specialty.)
(The art student's skilled scissor work)
(Neat and straight)
(Meanwhile, right beside her)
(Half-hearted Sun Young)
(Quick and rough versus slow and pretty)
(Her dried laver is ready.)
Do I...
- Wrap it roughly. Do it your way.
- Roughly?
Just wrap it your way.
(Try to wrap it your way.)
Small enough for one bite.
(Placing a small amount of rice for one bite)
(Rolling)
(Although she's never had it before)
(Making chungmu gimbap while imagining how it should look)
Whatever.
(It looks quite convincing.)
(Meanwhile)
( The half-hearted team finishes chopping the potatoes.)
Okay, it's done. The hurried potatoes are coming.
(Everything moves along smoothly, perfectly in sync.)
(You Seok is blanching squid.)
- Jung Ah.
- Yes?
- Stop blanching it.
- Is it enough?
It should be cooked.
(When one thing gets approved)
Shall I chop the chilli peppers to put in the soup?
- Shall I chop the chilli pepper...
- Jung Ah.
- Stop blanching it.
- to put in the soup?
- Is it enough?
- It should be cooked.
The water... What?
Shall I chop the chilli peppers to put in the soup?
- Yes, Cheongyang chilli peppers.
- Okay.
- Two or three?
- Two should be enough.
Jung Ah.
Does the rice normally stick to your hands?
Ma'am?
Is this enough, or do you need more?
You don't brush sesame oil on chungmu gimbap, right?
(Chef Yum suddenly freezes.)
Wait, I forgot to make the seasoning.
(Seasoning for the squid and fishcake)
Wait a minute.
(What was I going to do?)
My goodness.
Could you put a soup stock pack in the broth?
- I was cooking it with plain water.
- Do I rinse it after blanching?
- No.
- Okay.
(She almost made the soup with plain water.)
(Sighing)
(There's so much chaos.)
(She finally starts making the seasoning.)
(To chopped green onions and Cheongyang chilli pepper)
This is done.
(Pouring chilli powder)
(3 tablespoons of soy sauce)
I get to see you make this dish. I didn't know how to make it.
Hold on. How much did I add so far?
(1 tablespoon of confusion)
(A tiny bit of sweet green plum syrup)
(1 teaspoon of crushed garlic)
(Ginger juice to remove the squid's fishy smell)
(A drizzle)
(After adding a generous amount of starch syrup)
Jung Ah, do we wrap it like this?
(Another confirmation request comes in.)
- Of course.
- Okay.
(Tasting it since she picked it up)
- Sun Young.
- It's delicious.
That was so natural.
(Undeterred by the attempts to interfere)
(Stir until everything is evenly mixed.)
(Finally, drizzle in some sesame oil.)
(The mouthwatering seasoning is ready.)
(It's time to add squid and fishcake to season them.)
(Mix well until the seasoning is evenly absorbed.)
(Sprinkle on sesame seeds as the finishing touch.)
(The perfectly seasoned spicy squid and fishcake)
You eat this with the gimbap you made.
- Try some squid.
- Gosh, Jung Ah.
(The first bite to the youngest who's never had chungmu gimbap)
With the kimchi we made yesterday,
plate them together beautifully.
(Jung Ah, what is this?)
- This is insane.
- Okay?
This is insane.
Please plate them well.
- I'm going over there now.
- Okay.
(Heading off to finish the pollock roe and tofu soup)
(Running around everywhere)
Everything including radish and potatoes should be cooked.
(Adding pollack roe)
(Adding tofu)
(Salted shrimp for the soup appears.)
To keep it clean without bits floating around.
(Using only the shrimp brine to keep it clean and clear)
(For an extra boost of umami,)
(add a splash of fish sauce.)
(Adding green onions and Cheongyang chilli peppers)
It's all done.
(It's ready once it boils vigorously.)
- All the dishes are ready.
- Right.
The gimbap is almost ready.
(All they have to do is make gimbap.)
(Approaching quietly)
(Staring)
- Do you need something?
- No.
Are you worried about us?
- Aren't we too slow?
- No, not at all.
- Are we too slow?
- Just wrap it roughly.
Wrap it roughly. Don't make it perfect.
(Not exactly an easy setup for wrapping roughly)
(Don't feel pressured.)
(He wraps one nicely.)
(After giving a bite to Yoon Seo,)
(he takes a bite.)
It tastes good when you eat it like this.
(A sudden turn in the gamer's mind)
(Thinking)
Okay.
The food looks amazing.
It looks great.
(Whispering)
- What?
- In one of them,
- Wasabi?
- why don't we add wasabi?
(Wasabi)
Let's finish making it first.
Okay. Wait.
- You know what?
- One of us might eat it.
The one who comes up with the idea always gets it.
No, I'll avoid it.
Let's see.
(The wasabi is in the kitchen.)
(Smiling)
- What is it?
- It's nothing.
The thought of eating makes me happy.
It looks so good.
(It will be good.)
(Wasabi)
(After slipping it into his pocket,)
(Phantom Thief You Pin walks away without a trace.)
(Did you get it?)
(I got it.)
(Let's see.)
- Excuse me.
- Bowls for soup.
I brought out the bowls for soup.
Where are they?
- Are they on the table?
- I brought them out with a ladle.
Okay, then I'll serve it.
- Over there?
- Yes.
Just set the table.
Gosh, I put in a lot.
(There's no going back now.)
This is incredible.
(She has no idea what's going on.)
- It looks delicious.
- Viewers, in my opinion,
this will be the best meal on Fresh off the Sea.
- Did you add it in?
- A line of it.
- Isn't that too much?
- Is it?
Of everything I saw on Fresh off the Sea,
- it's what I want to eat the most.
- Really?
It looks so delicious.
Whatever.
Since you don't know which one it is, you mix them.
I don't know anymore.
The food looks amazing.
Gosh, it looks good.
(I don't care who gets it.)
(The random wasabi game is ready to begin.)
(Who will get the lucky chungmu gimbap?)
(Nervous)
- Let's go.
- Let's eat.
(A simple breakfast prepared by the four siblings)
Jung Ah, it looks delicious. I can't wait.
Jung Ah, it looks so good.
- Don't you think?
- Yes.
- There's pollack roe in it.
- That's great.
This smells really good.
(Spicy seasoned squid and fishcake)
It looks so good.
(Tangy radish and cabbage kimchi that was made yesterday)
I can't believe we made chungmu gimbap at home.
(And gimbap rolled by the youngest siblings)
(But there's 1 hidden trap.)
(The 4 siblings' 1st breakfast is ready.)
Thank you for the food.
Bon appetit.
- Bon appetit.
- Enjoy your food.
(Everyone reaches for the chungmu gimbap first.)
- Pit-a-pat. It looks delicious.
- Do I wrap this with...
With rice.
(Yoon Seo also takes a bite.)
- It's good.
- Yes.
(Everyone takes a big bite of the chungmu gimbap.)
With some squid.
(Walking on eggshells)
(The wasabi masterminds are sitting on edge.)
(Meanwhile, the older sisters are completely at peace.)
Squid and fishcake.
It tastes amazing.
(Stopping)
Did you put mustard in it?
(Startled)
(A guilty look is written all over his face.)
What?
(What's the matter?)
(Groaning)
- Come here.
- Where's the wet tissue?
- Was that your first bite?
- How did you eat that...
as your first bite?
(She makes a run for it.)
(Screaming)
(Soothing the shocked stomach with cold water)
- I didn't see it coming so fast.
- On an empty stomach...
I thought it'd take time.
I was suspicious as soon as she grabbed it.
(As soon as Jung Ah grabbed gimbap)
(Frozen)
(Realising what happened and suffering the burning pain instead)
(He can't keep a straight face.)
These guys are dangerous.
- Was it a candid camera?
- Yes.
How spicy is it? Give it to me.
Let's see how spicy it is. I like mustard.
You added a lot.
This is no joke.
I squeezed it out.
I can't believe...
- it was your first bite.
- You Seok, I thought...
You added a line of wasabi in it?
(The youngest siblings' surprise is a success.)
(Giving a look)
- Take them out now.
- There isn't anymore.
- There was only one.
- You're a lucky girl.
- You got picked.
- Picked for what?
- That's so funny.
You're picked as the deity of luck today.
- The deity of luck?
- Yes.
Your day will be full of good fortune today.
(They start eating again with the deity of luck.)
I thought, "Shall we wrap one with wasabi?"
(Sun Young tries the seasoned squid and fishcake.)
It tastes excellent.
(A bite of the delicious seasoned dish...)
(and a bite of gimbap)
(When you eat the plain chungmu gimbap,)
(you naturally crave the spicy seasoned squid and fishcake.)
Jung Ah, it's very spicy.
Right.
(Doesn't it make it tastier?)
- I can't stop eating it.
- I know.
(Once you take a bite,)
(you can't stop.)
(The spicy flavour is addictive.)
It's perfectly seasoned.
(Jung Ah's seasoned squid and fishcake is deliciously spicy.)
- It's so good.
- Jung Ah, it's really good.
The seasoned fishcake is really good.
Yes, it's very good.
(Feeling proud)
You can also make this at home.
(We can make it too?)
Jung Ah, did you add dried chilli in it?
No, I didn't.
- You didn't?
- No.
Remember the Cheongyang chilli pepper you chopped for me?
Right. And starch syrup.
What else did you add?
- Garlic.
- Chilli powder.
- Chilli powder
Thick soy sauce.
A bit of green plum syrup.
Some ginger juice.
You added ginger too?
(Gosh, a lot goes in it.)
You blanched squid and fishcake lightly.
Yes, and I also added some sesame oil.
- It takes a lot of work.
- It's done in no time.
- You made it fast.
- Yes.
She's like Bob Ross.
You know the painter, Bob Ross?
He says, "Isn't it easy?"
- Right.
- You think, "Wait a minute."
When you try it,
you have no idea.
You made it well too.
And I think...
- Yoon Seo studied fine arts.
- Right.
- Me?
- You made the gimbap beautifully.
- The gimbap?
- It turned out so pretty.
People who majored in art have a special touch.
Right. They're different.
(The youngest is trapped in a cage of compliments.)
- I made it with You Seok.
- It looks so pretty.
(It's a work by Yoon Seo and You Seok.)
Other than sesame oil, what did you add to the rice?
- Did you add a bit of salt?
- A bit of seasoned salt.
- Jung Ah told me...
- You added the perfect amount.
- Good job.
- You did well.
(With all the compliments, she can't hide her smile.)
I have to try this. I've been dying to try it.
What is it called? Pollack roe soup?
I seasoned it with salted pollack roe and salted shrimp.
(Sun Young and Yoon Seo try a sip at the same time.)
It's good.
(Humming)
Isn't it light and clean?
- This is why...
- It's very clean.
(A clear broth that's light enough for breakfast)
- The broth is amazing.
- Isn't it good?
(Exhaling heavily)
(Look at this guy.)
The old man inside him is coming out again.
(Tough Captain Kang whom they met yesterday)
(He reappears today.)
(Exhaling)
(Moaning)
(The reactions get more intense with every bite.)
The broth is very nice.
(The clean broth wins over the captain's palate.)
It's easy and simple to make.
It tastes much better than anything you buy.
You use good ingredients when you make it at home.
- I love this.
- Isn't it ripe?
After just one day.
(The radish and cabbage kimchi is aged perfectly after one day.)
(Crunchy)
(A satisfying crunch is an added bonus.)
While lying here, I...
(The refreshing radish and cabbage kimchi is...)
(also the perfect match for chungmu gimbap.)
(The breakfast tastes even better as it's shared.)
Gosh. It's so good.
(It tastes good too.)
It's really good.
- The weather is so nice.
- Right?
(It's the perfect beginning of the day.)
What kind of work are we going to do today?
- Will you tell us now?
- Where will we go?
- You'll know when you get there.
- Really?
- You won't tell us until then?
- They won't tell us.
- I thought we'd find out by now.
- They won't tell us even now?
(The youngest members are anxious.)
What's the point of finding out now?
We'll find out when we get there after a 20-minute drive.
I need to prepare myself emotionally.
- Gosh, I'm so full.
- I didn't know this was here.
You said we'd leave at 11am, right?
- What time is it now?
- It's 10am.
Let's catch a quick 30-minute nap.
Go ahead and take a nap.
The food coma must've kicked in.
Right. My blood sugar spike just kicked in.
- Right. Go ahead and take a nap.
- Okay.
Time to split up, you guys.
- But hold on...
- We're still...
- You'll talk without me.
- We're still eating.
Give us a second, Sun Young.
Go on and take a nap. We'll be talking about interesting stuff.
- No.
- You can keep the door open.
Keep the door open so you can hear us.
- Keep it open like last night.
- You heard us last night.
(Should I take a nap or not?)
- Seriously.
- She left the door open...
- not to miss anything.
- She heard everything.
She heard almost everything before she fell asleep.
(Don't have fun without me.)
- I thought there was no camera.
- It was fun.
It was so funny.
Nobody has ever kept talking to me like you guys did.
Yoon Seo and I went outside to stargaze last night.
- Did you?
- Yes.
- Wasn't it like a drama?
- It was.
Right? I felt like we were at a place like...
The Big Dipper was clearly visible. It was really nice.
Didn't you...
feel a spark or something romantic?
(Shaking his head)
- You were alone with her.
- We just...
enjoyed watching the sea and the sky.
Sorry to disappoint you.
- Sorry.
- You didn't feel a thing?
No.
- But it was really nice, right?
- Yes, it was really nice.
You two are like close siblings.
(She seems a bit disappointed. "I see. You two are like siblings.")
Let's warm up a bit before we head out.
- Okay.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors...
to choose today's instructor.
(Winking?)
(Chuckling)
- Sounds good.
(Grinning)
(They give off a subtle suspicious vibe.)
Sounds good.
(Earlier, while Sun Young was gone...)
Didn't we plan to exercise today?
- Feel free to use it.
- Right before we head out.
Who will be the instructor?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Yesterday...
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
But let's rig the results.
How?
We'll throw rock, then scissors, and then paper.
- Rock, scissors, and then paper?
- Rock, scissors, and then paper.
- So... Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(They came up with a little plot, led by the playful You Seok.)
It'll be decided within three rounds.
Are you sure we should play rock-paper-scissors?
- Yes!
- I'm a pro at that game.
Sun Young, are you good at rock-paper-scissors?
- No.
- Are you bad at it?
Yes.
(You'll end up in last place anyway.)
Are you?
The four of us will play the game.
- The loser will be the instructor.
- Okay.
- Here we go.
- Ready or not,
- rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Rock, rock, paper, rock)
Oh, yes.
(We didn't expect this.)
- From now on, it's war.
- You little...
From now on, it's war.
(Come over here, you punk.)
(Quiet down! We might get caught.)
- Why? What are you going to do?
- We'll play rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
- Go ahead. Ready.
- Ready or not,
rock-paper-scissors.
(Scissors, rock, scissors)
- I'm not the one either.
- You aren't?
- Seriously.
- What? I said it was war.
He's the one who started this. Let's do it.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Yoon Seo wins.)
We'll follow our instructor's lead.
- Follow my lead.
- Got it.
Please show us some good exercises for the back.
- This is good for your back.
- Okay. Good.
- Like this?
- One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
- One...
- I feel like...
- You should swing your hips wider.
- My hips might just snap.
- Move your hips more.
- My hips are about to snap.
Three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
- Two, two, three, four, - We're only doing this move?
- five, six, seven, eight.
- It really feels great for my back.
- One, two.
- Okay. Let's get going.
- I feel so refreshed.
- Right?
- Oh, my. Instructor.
- Yes?
- That was great.
- Let's hurry up and head to work.
Hey.
Dear me. My legs... Oh, gosh.
Put your seatbelt on, please.
- I did.
- We must put our seatbelts on.
(He plays music right away.)
That's Mr. Lee Chan Hyuk's song.
(That's Mr. Lee Chan Hyuk's song!)
Yes, you're right, Mr. Lee Chan Hyuk.
We're leaving now.
I wish Mr. Lee Chan Hyuk could come and sing the song for us.
- Right by our side.
- Whenever we go to work.
Won't he come visit us?
(Waiting for Mr. Lee Chan Hyuk who is not going to come...)
(They sing along together.)
(Sorrowful)
(On a cloudy day)
(On a sunny day)
(Even on a heart-breaking day)
(We will be working hard every single day.)
(Sentimental)
I wonder what kind of work we'll do.
(I wonder what kind of work we'll do today.)
(While singing along, they suddenly start worrying about today's work.)
- We won't know until we get there.
- I think it's horse mackerel.
Let me check Tongyeong horse mackerel online.
I should've taken a photo of the map.
(They still have no idea what they're going to do.)
They usually fish horse mackerel in this area.
(Is today's labour fishing horse mackerel?)
It'll be scorching hot if we get on the boat at noon.
It might not be fish.
(The experienced member's hunch)
They probably wouldn't be doing fishing work at this time of day.
Right? It's hard to predict.
Right. I have no clue.
Fishing work at this time of day?
- We're almost there.
- We'll be working by the sea here.
They're heading toward the boat.
That... My gosh. I see a huge boat.
- You see a boat?
- Where?
I see a very large boat.
(They see a large boat as they arrive at the destination.)
(I guess we're going to get on a boat again.)
(Anxious)
- Brace yourselves, guys.
- Yes, ma'am!
- Understood!
- Oh, my.
- We're going to work with them...
- Seaweed!
- Seriously?
- Look at the seaweed.
- They're prepping the seaweed.
- Seaweed.
- So we'll handle seaweed.
- Right.
(All they can see out the window is seaweed?)
(The siblings' second assignment: Wild rock seaweed)
(Gyeonnaeryang, a narrow strait between Tongyeong and Geoje)
The sea is very clean in this area.
(The powerful currents of the South Sea nourish...)
Seaweed can only grow naturally in this area.
It's organic wild rock seaweed.
(The powerful currents of the South Sea nourish...)
(the organic wild rock seaweed.)
It was offered to the king in the past.
It's been harvested since then.
(In the past, it was served as a royal tribute to the king.)
We harvest this type of seaweed...
only for 15 days a year.
(It can only be harvested 15 days out of the whole year.)
(The precious treasure of the sea)
Come and enjoy our tasty seaweed.
(The second seasonal food, Gyeonnaeryang wild rock seaweed)
So it's seaweed. We'll be dealing with seaweed.
What are we going to do with it? Are we going to harvest it?
Today, you will be working with...
- wild rock seaweed.
- Got it.
- We love it.
- Wild rock seaweed.
The wild rock seaweed in this area...
can only be harvested 15 days a year.
- Really?
- Is it harvesting season right now?
- That's amazing.
- You'll be working with...
- very rare wild rock seaweed.
- Yes.
As always, before you get to work,
we're going to do a draw that will determine your fate.
Come on. Stop lying.
Will some of us stay on land, just like yesterday?
Will only two of us get on a boat?
We all should work together.
What kind of draw is it?
Will some of us stay on land?
Are you serious? Only two of us will get on a boat?
First, grab one each at the same time.
- Okay.
- But don't pull it out yet.
- Just grab one?
- Let's go.
- We shouldn't pull it out?
- Don't pull it out yet.
- Just grab one each.
- We should just grab it.
I pick this one.
- It's seaweed.
- I'll just take the last one.
What should we do? Should we just grab it?
- One...
- Yes.
One, two, three.
How long is it?
(Long seaweed, short seaweed, long seaweed, short seaweed)
Mine is the longest of all.
Mine is long.
We got the long ones. Are we the ones going out to the sea again?
- Don't lie to us.
- What about the short ones?
- Don't lie to us. What's our task?
- Don't lie to us.
Jung Ah and Sun Young...
who drew the short pieces...
(What could be the older members' fate?)
- will get on the large boat.
- I see.
Are we getting on a small one?
- Is the large boat better?
- Hold on a second.
- Is this a bad one?
- Wait.
Hold on.
Since we drew the long ones, we should be on the large boat,
- not the way around.
- We should be on the large boat.
We should be on the large boat because we picked the long ones.
Why isn't the seaweed length proportional to the boat size?
- They're inversely proportional.
- Stop complaining.
- Just do as the director says.
- Just do as you're told.
- But why are they...
- Jung Ah says so.
- inversely proportional?
- By the way,
- we're on the same team again.
- Understood.
- We picked the bad ones again.
- Please explain to me.
(The pointless debate went on for a long time.)
- If we go far out to sea...
- I'm sure...
- our tasks are equally hard.
- Right, they must be.
Now,
please change into your work clothes.
Then we'll start working.
Okay. Let's go.
- I'm ready.
- Let's do this.
(The workaholic Captain Yum quickly hops aboard.)
(Full of enthusiasm)
Is that it? The one right next to this boat?
(After that, Yoon Seo...)
(and You Seok get on their boat.)
Guys, see you later.
(Everyone is on board now.)
(The older members' boat, the youngest members' boat)
- Jung Ah.
- Yes?
- Let's come back in one piece.
- See you soon.
- We'll be back with deep pockets.
- Okay.
(She's proud of Yoon Seo.)
- Hello.
- Hello, Captain.
Please take good care of our members.
You guys are in for a rough time.
- Will it be hard?
- Yes. This is a really tough job.
It really is.
- Is this really a tough job?
- Yes.
- Really?
- What did he say?
- That it's going to be tough.
- Is this really a tough job?
- You're lying, Captain.
- I'm telling you the truth.
(The boat engine is on.)
(The boat leaves before the members run away.)
- Why?
- Is it that hard?
You'll have to work with all your might.
- With all our might?
- Yes.
We'll have to work with all our might?
(How hard is it that they have to work with all their might?)
(Later on...)
(Gosh! Hold on.)
(Help!)
(Oh, no! Sun Young!)
(Shouting)
(Screaming)
(Shaking)
(The warning about working with all their might...)
(was not a joke.)
(The toughest task in the show's history)
(I don't think we can go home today.)
(The brutal labour will be revealed shortly.)
You've got this, guys!
Let's do this!
(They cheer up with Yoon Seo's positive energy.)
I feel prepared as I braced myself before coming here.
- At least this wasn't unexpected.
- Right.
- The scent of the sea is nice.
- It's so nice.
Jung Ah and Sun Young are on that boat, right?
(The two boats are heading to the harvesting spot side by side.)
I feel comfortable on the boat now.
- We've gotten used to the boat.
- That's right.
- I even took the wheel yesterday.
- This is a piece of cake.
I think we can all ride the same boat, with me driving.
(They're so confident now that they've been on a boat a few times.)
Let's sit back and make ourselves at home.
(The show-off captain is back.)
(The boat slows down.)
What?
(Then the boat stops in the middle of the sea.)
- This must be the harvesting spot.
- Right, I think that's the case.
I think this is it.
This must be the harvesting spot.
(They arrived at the seaweed harvesting spot.)
(The older members' boat, the youngest members' boat)
(Numerous boats are already here, battling the seaweed.)
I can sense the tension in the air.
(The toughest labour will take place on this battlefield.)
(What kind of labour is it?)
(It will be revealed shortly.)
Let's get to work now.
- Yes, sir.
- Yes, sir. What should we do?
(Completely disciplined)
(He solemnly raises the "weapon" for today's battle.)
Oh, my. It's so...
(A long pole that never seems to end?)
It's too heavy for women.
(Is this long stick the harvesting tool?)
(Wobbling)
(Wobbling, flinching)
Oh, my goodness.
(The length of the pole is intimidating.)
This...
We're using this long pole...
(The captain of this boat raises the long pole as well.)
Are we pulling the seaweed up with this pole?
(We're going to pull the seaweed up with this pole?)
This pole is 9.3m long.
- It's 9.3m long?
- It's 9.3m long.
And it weighs...
about 12kg to 13kg.
It's heavy.
(Finally, the truth has been revealed.)
(Here's why it's brutal labour.)
(It's all because of this incredibly long pole.)
(This pole has been designated as a national heritage. It's called...)
(Teulitdae)
(It's designed to be long to harvest seaweed from the deep sea floor.)
If you push it deep into the water,
(When you push the teulitdae all the way down to the bottom...)
it reaches the seaweed at the bottom.
The tip just reached the bottom, in the middle of the seaweed.
(The teulitdae has settled right into the seaweed forest.)
Next, you spin the handle. And then the seaweed...
(Spin the handle with the teulitdae firmly on the bottom.)
If there's seaweed down there, it'll coil around the teulitdae.
(The seaweed coils tightly around the teulitdae.)
After spinning the handle a few times...
(When there's enough seaweed coiled around the teulitdae...)
You pull it out when the seaweed is wrapped around the teulitdae.
(It's time to pull it out of the water.)
(The seaweed emerges from the water, wrapped around the teulitdae.)
(It's so easy, isn't it?)
- That's amazing.
- Right.
(The added weight of the seaweed makes it twice as heavy.)
(Lastly, you shake the seaweed off the teulitdae, and that's it.)
- This is how it's done.
- I see.
- This is how you harvest seaweed.
- Yes.
(It weighs about 30kg to 40kg. This work takes immense expertise.)
Do you want to try it?
- Yes. It looks very heavy.
- It's heavy.
(Will the older members do it well?)
- Try to put it into the water.
- Got it.
Here we go.
(As soon as they lift it up, they can feel the massive weight.)
(It's still too heavy for even two people to lift easily.)
(Gasping)
He said we should keep it close to the boat.
- First...
- Move it toward the bow.
- Toward the bow.
- Got it. Let's lift it again.
Toward the bow... Gosh.
I'll move to this side, Jung Ah.
(Just lifting it up and putting it in the water is already a struggle.)
- Step over to this side.
- Got it.
(They're being dragged by the teulitdae just like seaweed.)
All right. Let's do it this way.
- Okay. All right.
- Now, push it into the water.
- Plunge it quickly.
- Pushing it... Let's do it quickly.
- As quickly as possible.
- Right.
- It should be locked into place.
- Keep pushing it.
(They barely managed to get it into the water.)
(But the teulitdae keeps floating back up because of buoyancy.)
(It's almost at the bottom, but it's still fighting back.)
Push it all the way down until it reaches the bottom.
(Floating back up)
It will strike the bottom if you plunge it quickly.
- It won't reach the bottom.
- Wait until it's all the way down.
It'll strike the bottom when it's all the way down?
(Grunting)
(Chuckling)
(Floating back up)
At this rate, you won't even get enough seaweed to make a side dish.
That's not true. We can do this.
- It just hit the bottom.
- It hit the bottom.
- We should spin the handle now.
- Now, spin the handle.
(Finally, it seems like the teulitdae hit the bottom.)
- Spin it.
- I'll do it.
I think spinning the handle is easier. I'll hold the pole.
Jung Ah, you spin it.
It's hard to hold the pole. Goodness.
(Goodness)
(Oh, no)
(She might get hurt while trying to harvest seaweed.)
Spinning it will feel different once the seaweed wraps around.
- You can feel that?
- Yes.
- It becomes heavy.
- I see.
Hold on. I can feel its weight...
- when it wraps around?
- That's right.
(Does it mean the teulitdae is...)
It's not at the bottom, is it?
It should strike the bottom.
It should be at the bottom.
(It's spinning around without settling on the bottom.)
- It hit the bottom.
- Right. Spin the handle.
Okay. I'll spin it.
(Will they be able to harvest any seaweed by the end of the day?)
Gosh.
(Grunting)
- You're so bad at this.
- Jung Ah, can you move aside?
You wouldn't survive on Geoje Island.
(Even so, they keep spinning it with every ounce of their strength.)
- Because this is so heavy...
- Hold on a second.
Oh, my. We got it.
Awesome.
(As they spun the handle, the teulitdae became heavier.)
Pull it out now.
Let's see if you can survive on Geoje Island.
(Gulping)
(Combining their strength, they pull it out slowly.)
Oh, we got a little.
Sir, we got a little bit of seaweed.
(It's not a lot, but they succeeded in getting it out of the water.)
- Let's bring it safe on board.
- In the opposite direction...
- Check this out.
- Okay.
Why is there a rock stuck to the seaweed?
(Because it's wild "rock" seaweed.)
- This is called wild rock seaweed.
- Yes.
- It's organic.
- I see.
- It grows on rocks.
- Oh, I see. It grows on rocks.
There are rocks everywhere down there.
- So it's attached to rocks?
- Yes.
(That's why a rock tags along sometimes.)
Now we need to...
(Carefully separate the seaweed from the teulitdae.)
- Cut it and toss the rock.
- Okay.
(And that's how you harvest the top-quality wild rock seaweed.)
Hold on. You throw out this part, right? Do you eat this part too?
We eat that seaweed sporophyll.
- Oh, I see.
- Seaweed sporophyll.
I like seaweed sporophyll.
(You can only harvest it only when it comes out with a rock.)
This must be the finest product, right?
(They even got seaweed sporophyll, which is very rare, from the start.)
I really love seaweed.
(Sniffing)
(While the older members are lost in the joy of their first harvest...)
When the seaweed wraps around,
- Yes.
- it gets harder to spin the handle.
(Meanwhile, the youngest members are still learning how to do it.)
- It's really hard for a beginner.
- For a beginner.
Spin the handle a few times and pull it up when you get seaweed.
- Oh, my. Look at that.
- And you get seaweed...
- You get seaweed like this.
- That's amazing.
This is considered a small amount.
- Is this a small amount?
- Once you pull it on board,
you can untangle it from the teulitdae.
Just put it on top of the seaweed.
So this is wild rock seaweed.
Yes, this is wild rock seaweed.
- We're filling the boat with this.
- That'd be great.
(They've learned everything. Captain Kang steps up bravely.)
(I drove a boat yesterday. This is nothing.)
(Let's fill the boat with seaweed.)
(He's full of confidence.)
You have to plunge it vertically along the current.
(He quickly plunges the heavy teulitdae into the water.)
It's at the bottom now. Try to spin the handle.
(Now he has to spin the handle to get the seaweed to wrap around.)
Hold this part... That's good. Now, try to spin it.
(Squeaking)
(How well will Captain Kang do?)
(The handle doesn't spin easily.)
Try to spin it. Keep trying.
- Is it heavy?
- There's a rock.
In that case, shake it off.
Captain did it so easily, but you look...
(Looking quite different from the bold start)
Captain spun it so easily before.
(Captain Kang's pride has taken a hit.)
(Frowning)
(Laughing)
Gosh, it's...
It's not easy to spin it. It requires strength.
(You Seok, Captain)
- He's laughing.
- What if I harvest nothing?
(Psyching up)
The pole has caught between rocks.
(Exclaiming)
(Using every ounce of his strength)
Gosh. It requires lots of strength.
- I told you that it was tough.
- Come on.
You made it look so easy.
You did it so easily.
So, I thought it'd be easy.
Right.
If it doesn't spin, just take it out.
Pull it up. Yes.
(They decided to pull it up, instead of keep spinning it.)
Gosh. It's really heavy.
(He takes it out with Yoon Seo's help.)
Gosh. It's heavy.
(Surprised)
(Shocked)
Is this all I managed to harvest?
(A bit underwhelming)
At this rate, you won't make a living.
You won't make a living.
No one will feed him, if that's all he can do.
- They won't feed you.
- No.
(Joking)
You should have harvested more.
(Captain Kang's back looks dejected.)
We have to hurry and harvest more.
(Passing)
Okay. Try it.
(Yoon Seo takes over the pole right away.)
Diagonally.
- Pull it more.
- You have to pull it more.
- Pull it.
- Now, stick it in.
- Let it go, and it'll go in.
At first, just stick it in.
When you stick it in, it goes downward automatically.
(She confidently raised the pole and plunged it into the sea.)
It has reached the seaweed bed.
(It easily reached the seaweed bed.)
(Screaming)
It spins easily.
It rotates easily.
(Unlike Captain Kang, she spins it easily.)
If it turns easily, it means there is no seaweed.
Pardon?
- Really?
- It means there's nothing.
(Actually, the pole turned easily because there was less seaweed.)
We can't go home until we fill up the boat, can we?
No. You won't be going home.
Hey, I don't think we'll make it home today.
You won't go back home today.
- Bring it here.
- It spins so well.
- Bring it over here.
- Really?
(Laughing)
(Finding seaweed isn't easy either.)
Go further back.
- I need to go back.
- Yes.
(Screaming)
Did it catch on something?
(It instantly becomes harder to spin when there is more seaweed.)
Hold on.
(It gets stuck right away.)
Gosh, this is...
Hold on. What about Jung Ah and Sun Young?
Hold on.
(Doing her best while worrying about the older members)
(Grunting)
(Groaning)
Gosh. You're quite the worker.
(Proud)
I'm struggling.
How could I be the worker when I'm struggling so much?
(Embarrassed)
This is so hard.
(While saying it's hard, she suddenly spins it fast.)
(Fully determined)
(Groaning)
(She spins the pole with grit and determination.)
(Grunting)
(She keeps rotating it with all her effort.)
It's spinning.
(In the end, she even goes crazy.)
(Amazed)
It wraps the seaweed around the pole now.
(Spinning at a whole different speed than Captain Kang)
(Tough Yoon Seo)
Okay. Try pulling it up now.
Gosh. It's heavy.
It's okay.
(She retracts the pole confidently by herself.)
It's coming.
(Surprised)
Gosh. You're good at this.
(Jackpot!)
It's a lot. Do I shake it off?
You got more than I did.
You're a natural.
Captain, I'll come work here if I can't stay in Seoul.
(Yoon Seo finally found her calling.)
- You're good.
- Yes, she's good.
- Is it not bad?
- She's a great worker.
Try it again.
- I'll try it again.
- Will you?
I'll do it. Take some rest.
- Should we take turns?
- Yes.
- Plunge it.
- Throw it.
(Captain Kang tries it again, provoked by Yoon Seo.)
Reach the bed.
- Then turn it.
- Place the pole.
- Spin it more.
- Then I spin it.
(Surprised)
It has gotten easier for you. But as soon as I said that,
it has become tough.
If it doesn't turn at all, pull it up.
You can pull it up and try it again.
If there is only the head of the seaweed, it doesn't turn.
(Grunting)
Are you okay?
(Laughing)
(Groaning)
(You Seok only lets out weak little grunts.)
The current is too strong.
(Grunting)
(While the younger siblings do their best to harvest seaweed,)
Gosh. Turn it.
(the older siblings are going all in with the harvest too.)
Jung Ah, I'll turn it.
- You do it.
- I'll do it.
- Hold the pole.
- You spin it.
(The two of them work on it harmoniously.)
You shouldn't hold it like that.
You have to hold this part to spin it.
Okay.
Let's try it again.
- We caught some.
- Gosh.
(Grunting)
(Losing their sanity)
I'm giving birth right now.
- Gosh. Oh, dear.
- Gosh.
I've already given birth to two.
(While working, they understood what going all in feels like.)
Hold on.
(Laughing)
- Hey, this is...
- Wait.
This is an OB-GYN right here.
(Seaweed, please hold on.)
(Mom will get you out in no time.)
- Darn.
- Okay. Pull it now.
- One, two.
- Two.
(Giving the final push)
Here we go.
Okay.
(Grunting)
(Screaming)
(The unimaginable pain to give birth to seaweed)
(After their first seaweed-childbirth,)
(Grunting, their second seaweed child)
(Their third seaweed child)
Gosh. It's a lot.
(They pushed through, giving birth to seaweed consecutively.)
Go to the other side.
(This is not a simple seaweed harvesting.)
(This is a record of two moms' gruelling seaweed-birth story.)
Gosh. No.
I can make a living without working now.
Okay. Thanks.
Hold on.
(Reaching her limit)
(Mom Sun Young is wiped out.)
(Laughing)
- Well...
- My fingers hurt so badly.
Hold on.
(While the older sisters feel the pain of giving birth...)
My fingers.
Time to put on a disguise.
- Give me the work clothes.
- Yes. You can change inside.
What do I...
- And they'll come up.
- Okay.
(A man is speaking secretly with the staff.)
(Breathing in)
I think I'll get busted.
(He hurries to disguise himself in work clothes.)
(Who is this mysterious guy?)
Yes, put it over there.
It'll turn yellow.
(Park Hae Joon?)
When it's dry, it'll turn yellow.
Where are they? Are they out in the sea?
They are having a tough time.
(A secret guest who has arrived while the siblings are out on boats)
When I heard the three were on the show,
I was so happy.
(He decided to visit right away.)
I missed them all.
(Recently, he worked with Jung Ah and Sun Young...)
(on "Love, Take Two.")
(He played the father of You Seok...)
(in "When Life Gives You Tangerines.")
(Breathing)
I'm always grateful for You Seok.
I'm supposed to surprise him, right?
"I told you not to go on a boat!"
(That scene is...)
(It's the scene from "When Life Gives You Tangerines,")
(where he scolds his son not to get on a boat.)
(I wanted to get your boat back.)
(He urged his son not to get on a boat.)
(But he got on a boat again.)
"I told you not to go on a boat."
(He's going to scold You Seok again today.)
Won't they notice?
(He gets nervous now that he's about to surprise them.)
Aren't these too new? Don't they look so new?
Should I dip myself in the water?
(Nervous)
You Seok will come first, right?
(Shaking his legs out of nervousness)
He'll find out.
I shouldn't make eye contact.
(Pulling his mask closely)
(Will this prank work?)
(Sighing)
(In the meantime, on the older sisters' boat,)
(they're taking a short break.)
Jung Ah.
They're different.
What's that?
(The captain's harvesting skill is different.)
(Amazed)
(They can't help but be amazed by the amount.)
Look how tall this is.
- Seriously.
- It's crazy.
(It's as tall as a human.)
(Should I get back to it, then?)
(Captain Yum is motivated by the captain.)
Gosh.
(They control the teulitdae with more comfort now.)
- Seaweed is coming.
- Okay.
Rotate.
(They rotate the pole with ease now.)
I put it close to the boat.
(The process goes smoothly under Captain Yum's command.)
(Grunting)
(Groaning)
Is it tangled around the pole?
Gosh. It'll be so heavy.
(Captain Yum's power starts to show up.)
It's a lot.
Gosh. Look at the amount!
Gosh. This is... Seriously.
This is really...
(Plentiful)
You're good at it now.
(Should I try it once again?)
(Going for the 2nd round while keeping the momentum)
Gosh. These kids.
(The kids are messing with the wrong person.)
(Turn me back)
(To who I was before I met you)
(To turn it)
(As memories)
(She gets hurt by seaweed.)
(Jung Ah?)
(Turn me back)
I can't turn it anymore.
Come.
(Sun Young is on the move.)
(Turn me back)
I can't spin it.
(Switching players)
Look at her.
Sun Young's so good at it.
(Grunting)
(Turn me back)
(Syncing with Captain Yum's chant,)
She has incredible arm strength.
(Sun Young is now quick and efficient.)
(Spinning it like crazy)
You're good.
You can live on Geoje Island now.
(They finally won the right to move to Geoje Island.)
Let's pull it out now.
(Screaming)
(Amazed)
(They harvested as much seaweed as the captain did.)
(Straining)
(The older sisters have mastered the seaweed harvest skills.)
- Okay.
- Let's beat them.
- I know how to do it now.
(Groaning)
(The younger siblings put more effort in after that.)
- Do you need help?
- I think I'm fine.
- Take it out if it's too hard.
- No.
It's fun.
I won't be responsible if you have body aches.
(Somewhere between positivity and madness)
- It's so heavy.
- Let's see.
(Screaming)
It's a lot.
It's plentiful.
(She caught a big catch again.)
Good job.
(Laughing)
(Smiling)
(Scared)
You're so good at shaking off too.
- I'm amazing, aren't I?
- Let's get a boat.
Shall we?
(Bragging)
- I'll become a seaweed master.
- You're shaking it off well.
(Seaweed Master Yoon Seo gives the seaweed a good shake.)
Gosh. It's so fresh.
(Grunting)
(You Seok's gotten the hang of it, except for the grunting.)
You're a tough guy.
We're getting the hang of it, You Seok.
Yes. You're good at it now.
- Gosh. Look at you, You Seok.
- Gosh, You Seok.
- He's finally earning his keep.
- You Seok.
At this rate, you'd be able to work on your own soon.
(The younger siblings are harvesting with ease too.)
- You Seok.
- I got it now.
Do you get it now?
I'm going to quit my job in Seoul and come here...
- Yes, you can do that.
- to harvest seaweed with you.
Don't go. You're all mine.
They're all ours.
(Amazed)
Good job.
- Gosh.
- I'm a master now.
- It's plentiful. Gosh. It's a lot.
- Gosh.
(Seaweed piles up on both boats.)
- It's getting easier now.
- We got the hang of it.
Why don't you join me to harvest seaweed now?
- Should I?
- Yes.
- You're better than me.
- I might have to quit the show.
- Yes.
- He recruited me.
He said we're doing good now.
- I'll work here for 15 days.
- You're a natural.
- We're going back now.
- Okay.
Good job, You Seok.
You Seok, I think we harvested a lot.
It's a cartload.
Gosh. I got to understand how precious seaweed is.
Everyone is amazing.
What they do isn't easy.
- Wild rock seaweed is...
- It's the best.
harvested...
- I didn't know it'd be this hard.
- with great effort.
(A newfound appreciation for seaweed)
(We've learned a lesson again today.)
(While the younger siblings learn...)
(to appreciate ingredients,)
Load it up here.
(another man is also appreciating the value of seaweed.)
Be careful.
I'll do it. Where to?
This is uncomfortable. Really.
(Hae Joon helps the workers while waiting for the siblings.)
- Put it over there.
- Okay.
Then we work on it.
Place it as pretty as you can.
- Just like how pretty you are.
- Okay.
- Do you get it?
- Sure.
(Shy)
(He carefully lays out the seaweed harvested from the sea.)
You look like you're working with that hat and all.
They shouldn't recognise me.
His face can't be shown.
(He's serious about his disguise...)
(while they want to see his face.)
(Despite nobody watching,)
(he does his best to disguise himself.)
(In the meantime,)
(the younger siblings' boat approaches.)
The boat is approaching.
What?
(To fool them completely,)
(he goes with a cart.)
(He plans to approach them as one of the workers.)
I told you not to lend the boat.
What's with the shooting?
Go away!
I told you not to go on that boat. Why did you?
(People near him are surprised because his acting is too real.)
(He's totally into the character to pull it off perfectly.)
We're done!
It's just the beginning. We have to lay it out.
(The two have no idea what's coming.)
Is this it? Is this their boat?
(His first victims are approaching slowly.)
(The prank will begin in 5 seconds.)
I told you not to drive the boat!
Why did you take the boat?
(What's going on?)
I told you not to use the boat.
What's with the shooting?
Come back at once!
(Is he talking about our shooting?)
Who gives you the right to do whatever because you're shooting?
What are you shooting anyway?
I told you not to take the boat. Why did you take it?
(It's starting to get scary as he's talking about them.)
(The captain must be indifferent of the situation...)
(because he drives the boat closer to him.)
Who gives you the right to do whatever because you're shooting?
(The biggest crisis in Yoon Seo's life)
(Kneeling to apologise)
Look at these kids.
- Father.
- Gosh, You Seok.
Father.
(Laughing)
(Surprised)
(You Seok!)
You just got a little bit of seaweed.
- You little...
- Father.
I told you not to go on a boat.
- He told you not to.
- I wanted to get your boat back.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Come on. Seriously.
(Surprised)
For a handful of seaweed...
- Sure.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- Yes.
You've come so far.
- You've come all the way here.
- To Tongyeong.
(Bowing to his father as it's been a while)
Your father told you not to go on a boat.
It's unbelievable.
It's crazy.
- I'm embarrassed.
- Hold on.
- Yes, sure.
- Gosh.
You've travelled so far to get here.
What do we do with Jung Ah and Sun Young?
- We need to prank them now.
- Do we?
I'll show them.
They might not notice him.
You'll give it away when you talk.
My voice gives it away.
- Don't speak.
- Right.
- It'll be okay if he doesn't talk.
- Act natural.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
It doesn't look natural if he stays with us.
Do you want to stand back there with the staff?
You'll stay with the staff.
When they arrive, you can come with a cart.
(Plan 2: Appearing like a worker after hiding for a while)
But you're so tall and handsome.
How can I not be tall and handsome?
- Hunch over.
- Bend over a bit.
Gosh. It's refreshing
It's cool.
(The 2nd victims are just happy.)
I heard it was tough, but...
Wait, is that the boat?
The boat is coming.
(Coming inside the trap)
- They're coming.
- They're here.
They're coming.
(They're on the move right away.)
Hey!
(Diverting their attention by greeting them loudly)
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
I'll pretend not to know them in the back.
Hey!
(Hae Joon hides in the back like they planned.)
Are you okay?
It's seriously the best.
(They have no idea, thumbs up)
I give two thumbs up.
What was tough about that?
(They're the best.)
It was tough.
We just need to load the cart with the seaweed.
Gosh. Good job.
Okay.
- Gosh.
- What do we need to do?
- You need to load the cart.
- Load it here,
and he'll carry it.
Load it here, and he'll carry it.
(Working as planned)
- We...
- In here.
Put it in.
- Put it in.
(In the heat of the moment, he forgets the plan and speaks.)
(It's clearly Hae Joon's voice.)
(Glancing)
(Glancing again)
You got a lot.
I think I know this mister.
Who is he?
(Let me see your face!)
It is you, Hae Joon.
(In the end, he's caught.)
You were looking at him closely.
You came all the way here.
Yes, I did.
(But this jerk.)
Why didn't you get on the boat with us?
Why didn't he get on the boat?
You should've joined us. We could've harvested way more!
- I...
- Come on.
Help us.
- This?
- Hello.
- Yes.
- We got a lot, right?
- Yes, you did.
Who harvested them?
- Four of us did.
- We did.
- You all harvested them?
- Yes, we did it together.
It must've been tough.
- It was nothing.
I'll pull it.
We need to work on seaweed.
Time to hang them up.
- Time to eat.
- Food? Really?
(An enjoyable mealtime before the next work starts)
So you eat before you start working.
It's a meal.
What's the menu?
(Curious)
- One, two, three. Ta-da.
- What is it?
- It's seaweed soup.
- Seaweed soup.
Seaweed soup.
(Capturing the clean sea wholly)
- There's sujebi in seaweed soup.
- It's sujebi.
Seaweed sujebi soup.
- Really?
- They gave us so much.
(It can't taste bad.)
(It's cooked using wild rock seaweed caught here.)
Amazing.
(This is fresh off the sea.)
- It looks so delicious.
- Beef seaweed sujebi soup.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy your food.
(He tries the soup first.)
(Slurping again)
It's just the way I like it.
It's so tasty.
I love seaweed soup, and this is amazing.
(Eating kimchi too)
(Ecstatic)
(Sun Young tries the soup too.)
It's so tasty. This is awesome.
I love seaweed soup, and this is amazing.
(The rich flavour amazes him.)
(Everyone is exclaiming.)
- It's so good.
The soup is so thick and rich.
The soup is different.
(The soup is more savoury and thick thanks to wild rock seaweed.)
(Jung Ah tries wild rock seaweed.)
It's just the way I like it.
It's so tasty.
(Humming)
(It's just the way she likes it.)
(Taking another bite right away)
The seaweed is crazy.
I should try cooking this myself.
(It's perfect for Hae Joon too.)
Its texture is...
soft yet chewy.
(Wild rock seaweed has various textures.)
It's interesting.
(It tastes even better after the manual labour.)
It's chewy.
It's not just hard.
It's very soft...
(Slurp)
It's interesting.
(He is in love with seaweed sujebi soup.)
(A mouthful of seaweed)
(A mouthful of kimchi)
(Inhaling nonstop)
(He drinks the soup fiercely.)
(Entranced)
It tastes good even when you didn't work, right?
(Feeling guilty)
(Teasing him)
I made a plan to surprise you.
But it was a half-baked plan.
(Hae Joon was on an empty stomach since he came early in the morning.)
(It's not a sin to fall in love with seaweed soup.)
Tomorrow, we're having a cooking competition.
A cooking competition.
(One month ago, during the introductory meeting)
(The younger members wanted to cook for Jung Ah.)
(What do you like, Jung Ah?)
(I like curry!)
(Jung Ah, you have no idea how great of curry I make.)
(I'm an expert when it comes to curry.)
(Everyone is claiming themselves a curry master.)
(I'll start by caramelizing onions...)
(and cook it Japanese-style.)
(Caramelizing onions?)
(I don't do stuff like that.)
(That's not how you cook curry.)
(Sun Young, I have a feeling yours will taste bad.)
- Why?
- It'll taste plain.
(Insulted)
(That's not true.)
(Shall we make it a curry competition?)
(Shall we do a curry competition?)
I could never lose.
(It provoked the gamer's competitiveness.)
(I'll learn from a chef.)
(The curry competition has suddenly been decided.)
- Curry?
- That's the menu.
And I'm sitting it out.
They'll be joining. You should participate.
I'll definitely win.
(If I participate, I'll definitely win!)
- Do you cook often at home?
- Curry is easy.
(Actually, Hae Joon is...)
I'm not a bad cook.
- Are you good with knives?
- I'm not bad.
(He cuts radish with ease.)
(He mastered from bossam to rice cake soup.)
(The genius chef lost to the culinary world)
We can buy curry powder, right?
Of course. You need curry powder.
Which brand of curry will you use?
Or will it be Japanese-style?
(Listing out the types of curry)
Or hayashi rice?
(Look at him.)
- He's cooked it a lot.
- Of course.
Do you like beef, pork, or chicken?
You shouldn't tell him.
He sounds like a professional.
I'll end up in last place at this rate.
(Whining)
(Who will win the curry competition?)
How much...
are you giving us today?
Right.
How much are you giving us today?
(Very serious)
You should tell us how much we'll get for the work.
Even here, all Eun Myeong talks about is money.
(Suddenly back to "When Life Gives You Tangerines")
Eun Myeong.
- Father.
- Yes.
I'm trying to get your boat back.
(The dad is worried about his son.)
(The son wanted to get his boat back by harvesting seaweed.)
(The story of the good son Eun Myeong)
(I want the sequel.)
Do you like to jog? Will you join me tomorrow morning?
He's thinking about running tomorrow,
which means the work wasn't tough enough.
The work wasn't tough enough. We should run him into the ground...
so he can't run tomorrow.
(Terrified)
I didn't even think about it because I was set on working hard.
(Laughing)
(Gwan Sik attacks Eun Myeong fiercely.)
(It suddenly turned into a comedy.)
Eun Myeong, can I have more seaweed?
Can I have more seaweed too?
(The refill request continues.)
(It recharged them good after the hard work.)
(It was a fun mealtime.)
(They've finished two bowls each.)
This would sell so well.
I'm so full. I ate so much seaweed.
(Sun Young suddenly stands up.)
(She warms up slowly.)
Jung Ah taught me the workout which prevents backaches.
It prevents backaches.
Instructor, am I doing it right?
It is. Just do as you like.
(Just do however you feel like doing.)
- Did you learn it from someone?
- No, I made it myself.
It really helps you strengthen your back.
(Yoon Seo joins her.)
(Dancing)
- My back hurts too.
- Do this if your back hurts.
(Gosh, you guys...)
You need to pop your hips.
(Hae Joon joins the exercise.)
- Not front and back?
- No. It feels nice.
(I'm excited.)
Instructor.
(Unable to resist, Jung Ah joins them too.)
- My hips are...
- I'm so excited.
(A dancing machine)
(Are you sure? My hips don't know how to stop.)
- Your back doesn't hurt, right?
- It stretches nicely.
(Wiggling)
It feels nice.
The ladies must be wondering what we're doing.
(Laughing)
- They're following our dance.
- Where?
They're doing it too.
The dance spread so quickly.
(I heard it was fun.)
Yes, do it when your back hurts.
(Dance)
(Join us.)
My gosh.
- Thank you for the food.
- It was the best.
- This is so funny.
(It's time to work again.)
Let's hang the seaweed up.
(Let's hang the seaweed up.)
Hello.
- Hello.
Shall we hang up...
- Yes.
the seaweed you harvested from the sea?
- Okay.
(Seaweed labour Step 2: Drying the seaweed)
(Freshly caught moist wild rock seaweed)
We go out on a boat and harvest them.
(Cut off the holdfast of seaweed.)
And we dry them all.
(Hang them up on the drier one by one.)
(Under the warm sun of Gyeonnaeryang,)
We need to dry them for three days to be able to sell them.
(dry them out for 3 days.)
(Tasty and healthy wild rock seaweed is completed.)
It's dried naturally under the sun,
so it's yellowish.
(It's yellowish because it's dried under the sun.)
(Shall we start the work?)
(The first step to dry the seaweed: Setting up a drying rack)
Put it here.
- Put it here.
- Okay.
(Carrying it)
Stand facing each other.
- Yes.
- Do I spread them out?
- Yes, spread them out.
(Spread out the seaweed to dry.)
Spread them out evenly.
(Seaweed-drying Tip 1)
(Spread them out evenly so they will dry well.)
Evenly.
(Inputs "evenly")
(Flatten)
(Outputs "evenly")
Do I fill up the corner as well?
Yes.
They'll shrink as they dry up.
(Seaweed shrinks as it dries up.)
They shrink a lot when they dry up.
(You must fill up the whole rack without any empty spot.)
They shrink like that.
(That's how you make pretty seaweed.)
Is this thick enough?
No, make it thicker.
- Thicker?
- Or there will be holes.
- We can't have holes?
- No holes at all.
- Cover up all the empty spots.
- I see.
(Seaweed-drying Tip 2: Pile them up nice and thick.)
But not too thick.
It won't dry up.
(But it can't be too thick.)
(You must maintain the right thickness.)
The big ones don't dry up easily.
Cut up the big ones.
- Okay.
- They don't dry up easily.
- Yes.
(Laughing)
- She's a copycat.
- Yes.
How long have you worked here?
- Around a decade for me.
- A decade?
"For me."
(Her lies are on a whole new level.)
Ma'am, is this good enough?
No, you need more, mister.
Bring more.
The small one.
Here you go.
- That's enough.
- Yes.
(Very thorough)
I hope they dry well.
(Pressing them firmly)
Ma'am, is this all right?
I don't think you've worked for a decade.
You don't think so?
(Attacking her with facts)
Ma'am.
(Upset)
(Come back after 10 years.)
- Here.
- Thank you.
(They spread them out one by one.)
(The rack is very full.)
It's so full.
- Lift it up...
- Yes.
and move it to there.
- Over there?
- Yes.
(It's time to move the drying rack to a sunny spot.)
Hold there.
Careful.
(They start moving.)
There are legs underneath.
- The legs.
- Unfold them.
(Unfold the legs and put it down nicely.)
That's good. Enough space for people to walk around.
Okay, enough space for people to walk around.
(The first rack is completed.)
They must dry up well since it's very sunny nowadays.
Here comes more seaweed.
(Without catching a breath, they start on the next rack.)
I'll make it as pretty as possible.
(Meanwhile, Hae Joon is very enthusiastic.)
When you get married, you must have this seaweed.
(When you get married, you must have this seaweed.)
Yes, I will.
He's yet to get married.
(She thinks Hae Joon is a bachelor, but he's been married for 16 years.)
Goodness.
I would've gotten married already if I was good at making seaweed.
She saw you...
and thought you were a bachelor.
Yes. I'd get married right away.
(The seaweed bachelor feels happy.)
The bachelor will fill up this side of the rack.
(He's so funny.)
(But...)
(Piled up)
(There's just no end to the seaweed.)
There's more?
This takes a lot of effort.
It does.
It'll be very gruelling if you do this for a long time.
(You must spread out heavy seaweed under the burning sun.)
Goodness.
(It's hard for the passionate bachelor too.)
I thought nothing of it when I bought them.
(This is a seaweed nightmare.)
I thought this would be easy.
But it isn't.
(While everyone is struggling in the seaweed nightmare)
- Does it look like hair?
- It swishes.
Ma'am, I'd already put it here.
You can't take what I put here.
I stole it.
(Playful Yoon Seo steals You Seok's seaweed.)
Now I understand why people compare hair to raw seaweed.
It swishes a lot.
Swish.
(Like a baby doing a tactile play)
Seaweed.
(Yoon Seo is fascinated by the seaweed's texture.)
Goodness.
- Aren't you tired, Yoon Seo?
- No.
It's like making kimchi.
(Very goofy)
Where's the gap?
Don't show any gap.
Fill up the gaps.
(A cute threat to the seaweed)
(She's adorable.)
(The lovely youngest never stops smiling.)
- Let's go.
- Is it done?
One, two, three.
Watch your step.
My goodness.
(As they spread them out excitedly, they complete another rack.)
I should use more.
- Do you need more seaweed?
- Yes.
There are a lot of gaps.
(They continue to hang up the seaweed thoroughly.)
All of you are so good.
Really?
Thank you.
(They all look like experts now.)
(They fill up the drying racks together.)
- They're getting closer to us.
- Yes.
Goodness.
We filled up everything.
(Heave-ho)
- It feels a bit like farming.
- Yes.
Farming? Yes.
Like ploughing the field.
(Is the seaweed drying well?)
I feel satisfied looking at them.
(Just looking at them makes her feel satisfied.)
Is this the last one?
- It's already the last one.
- Really?
(It's their last rack already.)
Since we work on it together...
- It's over quickly.
You bond over work.
- And over a meal.
- Yes.
- You bond over work.
- Over work.
The weather is nice. This village is so lively.
- It's so pretty.
- Yes.
(The siblings' bond thickens today.)
(They scrape up the remaining seaweed...)
(and press it down together.)
- Let's go now.
- Let's go.
(The final rack is completed.)
The final one.
We're done.
- Right here.
- We're done.
- Yoon Seo, watch your back.
- Okay.
(The siblings filled up 9 racks.)
(The end of the seaweed labour)
Everyone, do the back dance.
Good job with the seaweed labour.
I'll pay you the wage.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- How much is it?
- How much?
(Payment time)
They said wild rock seaweed was expensive.
- Wild rock seaweed is expensive.
- And five of us worked.
And spinning that thing was so hard.
My gosh, how much is that?
- How much is it?
- That's a lot.
- Three.
- Three hundred?
Two hundred.
(200 dollars in total)
Two hundred?
We're rich.
We earned more than yesterday, right?
- Thank you.
- Two hundred dollars.
(Super elated)
Thank you for your hard work.
- Goodness.
- Thank you.
- I hope you enjoy it.
- Such precious seaweed.
- Thank you so much.
(Her gift for the siblings who worked hard)
- This is...
- What is it?
(Gyeonnaeryang wild rock seaweed fresh off the sea)
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
(3 days later)
(The seaweed harvested by the siblings...)
(were dried well...)
(under the warm sunlight of Gyeonnaeryang.)
(They became tasty wild rock seaweed and were shipped nationwide.)
It was very laborious.
We worked hard today.
Before we go back,
remember the deal...
you've made with us?
The weather is nice.
It'll be perfect to ride the cable car and the luge.
Can I make a 1-on-1 deal with the staff?
He said he could never lose in omok.
If you beat him in omok.
(He suggested an omok match with the luge on the line.)
A game of omok now?
- Here?
(But...)
- We're going to ride the luge?
- Right now?
We're going to ride the luge?
(It's bad news for Sun Young, who has used up her energy.)
Sun Young...
(She's exhausted.)
(Walking slowly)
- It's 35 dollars.
- Lose.
She told you to lose.
She did this.
They're so scary.
- Just You Seok.
- A quick match.
Go and play.
We'll set off first.
I'll get going.
- We elected the players too.
- Yes.
- We have three candidates.
- Okay.
- Out of the three candidates, - Do we choose?
choose one after hearing their keywords.
- Choose one.
- You'll play against them.
Sounds good.
We need to choose someone who is bad at it.
Number one, a global leader.
(Opponent candidate 1: A global leader)
- Okay.
- Number two, an engineering major.
- An engineering major.
Number three, a young brain.
(Opponent candidate 3: A young brain)
They all sound formidable.
An engineering major has nothing to do with omok.
But out of the three, the engineering major sounds like...
the most formidable player.
I'm curious to see who the global leader is.
Can someone even play omok globally?
Don't you agree?
Who plays omok globally?
He's right. The global leader is probably the worst at it.
- The global leader...
- I'm curious.
- Right.
The global leader is probably the worst at it.
Global?
What does that have to do with omok?
Just because someone is the UN Secretary-General...
doesn't mean he'll be good at playing omok.
- He's right.
- Yes. We'll go with global leader.
- Global leader.
Okay.
- Come on out, global leader.
- Come on out.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
(Who could the global leader be?)
- Jazz.
- I'm fine, thank you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yes.
He went to the School of Global Leadership, Sungkyunkwan University.
(He's an alum of the School of Global Leadership.)
Have you ever lost an omok match?
I've only lost at omok…
a handful of times.
- He's a strong player.
- Gosh.
(His confidence took a sudden hit when a master player showed up.)
All right.
No, we can do this. Let's ride the luge.
You got this!
(You got this, son!)
(The players take their seats for the match.)
- You got this.
- With permanent markers?
(Representing the siblings, the luge fanatic)
(Representing the production staff, the global leader)
(Let the match begin.)
- The global leader.
- Are you taking a picture?
(You Seok plays Black and moves first.)
(The global leader plays White and catches up.)
- You can finish this quickly.
- Okay.
(Once the match starts, Sun Young cheers for You Seok.)
(Locked in)
You Seok.
(Black makes the second move.)
He won.
Was that a good move?
I'm not sure.
(Stunned)
- You don't know?
- No.
- I thought you knew.
I don't play omok like that.
- I play omok purely by instinct.
- I see.
(He's so locked in that he doesn't hear the cheering.)
(Just then,)
(You Seok suddenly picks up the pace.)
(What move did You Seok make?)
(He blocked White's advance...)
He has many options.
(while opening the way for Black.)
Good job. That was brilliant.
He's winning.
- He's winning?
- He's really winning.
I think seven moves should be enough.
(He's sure he can win within 7 moves.)
(You Seok's relentless attack continues.)
(Hesitating)
Are you sure he's good at this?
There are so many options.
Even an amateur like me can see there are many options.
It's over.
(It's over.)
- It's a 4-3, so he can't stop me.
- He can't stop you.
(Whatever move White makes, Black wins.)
Gosh, we won!
We won? Gosh.
(Filled with joy)
- You won?
- You really won.
- Gosh, you...
- You really are good at this.
- Gosh, it's hot.
- You won.
- You're good at this.
- My face got tanned.
Are we all set?
Wait, so does that mean we're going to ride the luge?
Why were you cheering for him to win...
if you don't want to ride the luge?
(I'm doomed.)
Thank you.
(He earned both the luge tickets and a boost of confidence.)
Great job.
- Great job.
- It's over.
Let's go.
(It's time to go grocery shopping.)
Good work, everyone.
- Good work, everyone.
Gosh, Jung Ah. I really struggled...
- with the teulitdae earlier.
- Right?
- We didn't have the technique.
- We really didn't.
It was so heavy. It was so heavy, we were wobbling.
- So much so that it felt dangerous.
- It did.
Yoon Seo really pushed through with sheer determination.
I basically used my face strength to turn it.
That's how I did it.
(She scrunched up her face, putting her whole body into it.)
You really worked hard.
(Embarrassed)
We're having a few drinks tonight.
- They provide everything.
- Even alcohol?
- It's Dajji.
- I see.
- Unlimited drinks and alcohol.
(They're going to use the dining voucher...)
(they earned by harvesting sea squirts for Dajji.)
And If you want to go to karaoke, we can spend about 35 dollars.
I'm fine singing if it's just us,
but I feel embarrassed about to do it on TV.
I'm not a good singer.
I get too nervous to enjoy singing.
I don't think the viewers are expecting much.
I know they're not,
but I'm still embarrassed because I'm bad at it.
- "They're not expecting much."
- I don't feel confident.
(Flustered)
What do you want to do?
Are you really trying to think about the viewers?
If you want what's best for the viewers...
You have to sing, even if you can't.
Hae Joon, when you go to karaoke,
what kind of songs do you sing?
I'm more of a technical singer.
What? You use a lot of vocal techniques?
Gosh, that's probably pretty tiring to listen to...
after a few songs. Right?
(Looking forward to Hae Joon's vocal techniques at karaoke)
I should think about the ingredients I'll need for the curry.
Well, curry is...
You Seok...
said he has his own special recipe for curry.
- Really?
- He said it's a secret.
(Thinking)
Jung Ah, how do you feel about MSG?
It's fine if it tastes good.
We'll buy a packet of beef seasoning powder.
(We'll add some MSG.)
You're putting beef seasoning powder in curry?
I guess cooking is about technique.
I think he might have too many techniques for everything.
Have you heard of Park Poong?
(Poong as in Kim Poong, writer and master of fusion cuisine)
Since we're in Tongyeong,
we should make Tongyeong-style curry.
Really?
- With seaweed and sea squirt?
- Yes.
We should use seaweed and sea squirt.
- Seriously?
- Of course.
Seaweed and sea squirt in curry?
They might not go well with curry.
He wants to come in last.
We were here yesterday.
(They arrived at the supermarket while talking about curry.)
I'll wait in the car while you get groceries.
- You're not going with us?
- No.
Because I shouldn't see the ingredients you get.
(The contestants begin grocery shopping.)
(Park Poong heads straight to the fridge.)
- Hae Joon.
- Yes?
- How many...
- Why did I get so startled?
- How many carrots do you need?
- Only about half a carrot.
Right? Then I should get one more.
Goodness.
(Cautious)
(He quietly picks up a pack of tomatoes.)
He's using one, and I'm using half.
(Glancing at Sun Young)
Potatoes. Should we get one more?
It's getting intense.
Of course.
Who put these tomatoes in here?
The tomatoes? I wanted to eat some.
You wanted to eat some? Can I have one too?
For your curry or to eat?
- For my curry.
- Gosh.
(Feeling deflated)
(His secret ingredient was immediately discovered.)
- Should we get another pack?
- No, I don't need that many.
- I'm just going to use one.
- Who put the tomatoes in there?
- Me.
- Potatoes, carrots, onions. And?
- Are you putting in tomatoes?
- I'm doing it too.
I was going to do that.
We're all using tomatoes?
Gosh, this can't be happening.
was going to sneak some tomatoes into the cart.
- You thought of tomatoes?
- Tomato paste.
I was going to put in tomato paste.
Paste? Why don't you just make yourself ramyeon?
Tomato paste is just seasoned tomatoes.
Then why not just buy pre-made curry?
Let's each shop for our own ingredients.
(Grumbling)
(Thinking)
I'm going to hide this in my pocket...
and take it out at the register.
(Hiding)
(Spying)
What? Hey.
Then I'm doomed.
(Her plans fall apart because she can't find what she wanted.)
The brand I usually use...
Let's go get some ice cream.
- What?
- Nothing.
- Why are you being so secretive?
- You go ahead.
Excuse me, ma'am. Where can I find chicken stock?
- Pardon?
- Chicken stock.
You can just point me in the direction.
This middle section?
Why do you keep looking, Sun Young?
I'm not going to copy your ingredients.
Chefs, the curry showdown is about to begin.
(Fresh Curry Arena)
Welcome to the Fresh Curry Arena.
(The perfect setting for the curry showdown)
She's here.
- Gosh, she looks pretty.
- Satisfy Master Yum Jung Ah's...
- Hello.
- taste buds.
Let's begin the curry showdown.
My goal is to make sure it turns out well.
(Roh Yoon Seo: My goal is to finish it in time.)
If I don't come first, who will?
I'm going to win this, no matter what.
I'm going to make that 90s-style curry...
that we grew up eating.
I want to make something different.
(Cooking skills: Unable to determine)
(The four chefs go head-to-head to become the ultimate curry legend.)
(Out of the four different curries,)
(which one will win over...)
(Master Yum Jung Ah?)
Coming soon, the siblings' curry showdown.
(After the intense grocery shopping)
- Now that we've started, - You guys are so funny.
- it's a full-on battle.
- Is it?
We were in there trying to hide what we were picking out from each other.
Everyone's using all kinds of ingredients, including fruits.
It's so interesting.
- You Seok.
- Yes?
You're amazing.
- Why?
- You got your wish.
- I'm so happy.
- The luge.
No one else wanted to do it,
but you got your wish.
- Gosh.
- We're being led around by him.
Yes.
(Magnet Kang, actor: Leads the siblings around)
Gosh, You Seok. You have so many things you want to do.
- This vibe.
- Yes.
Houses tucked away in every little alley.
(They arrive at the village.)
I see the house.
Those are our bikes.
(After an uphill walk, they finally reach the Siblings' House.)
- You have bikes?
- Yes.
Welcome to the Siblings' House.
Ta-da!
Gosh, it's pretty.
(In awe)
Look at the flowers!
(Hae Joon, look at the flowers!)
(The yard is overflowing with peonies in bloom.)
Gosh, this house is so nice.
There's a vegetable garden here.
(Hae Joon is pleased to see...)
(the small vegetable garden on the roof.)
It would be nice to come up here at night and have a beer.
- Isn't it nice?
- It is.
(A simple, heartfelt remark)
I love Tongyeong.
I'm going to sleep like a baby tonight.
I can sleep like a baby right now.
- Let's take a break.
- Yes.
- Let's relax a bit.
(The siblings decide to take a break.)
(While Sun Young and You Seok lie down and rest,)
(Jung Ah and Yoon Seo are freshening up.)
Do you want me to do your hair?
Right now? You think you can do it?
If I try and fail, we'll just have to...
Just braid it like this.
(Art school graduate Yoon Seo opens her magical hair salon.)
(She's clearly nervous about her first customer.)
(With steady hands, she begins braiding Jung Ah's hair.)
It's cool that you know how to do this.
This is my first time.
- Did you watch a YouTube tutorial?
- I did.
- I'm not sure I can do a good job.
- It's okay. Don't worry about it.
I'm starting to see the shape of it.
My hair has gone flat...
from wearing a hat all day.
Are you braiding it for a ponytail?
Do you want a ponytail or pigtails?
I can't wear pigtails in Seoul, so I wanted to try them here.
- I get what you mean.
- Right?
When you're travelling,
you become more adventurous with your style.
(Yoon Seo continues to braid Jung Ah's hair while they talk.)
(Like a bird)
(They hear someone singing outside their room.)
Hae Joon's having fun.
(The only thing I can give you)
(He is captivated by the record player in the living room.)
(Is my love)
(He puts a carefully selected vinyl on the record player.)
We have to listen to this song. It's a classic.
What is it?
(Hae Joon turns up the volume.)
(The song has a very nostalgic feel.)
It's a government-sponsored morality song.
(A genre of songs promoted after the Japanese colonial period...)
(that carried messages of social education and moral instruction)
Every album was required to include at least one by law.
("Uh-hoya Dunggidunggi" by Lee Moon Se)
(Let's come together and share)
(Both the joys and the hardships)
(We're all familiar neighbours)
(Like one big family)
(A place full of warmth)
(Our village, a village of flowers)
(Wistful)
Listening to it now,
he actually sang it really well.
He's like my dad.
(Giggling)
(Hae Joon sat there listening to old songs for a while.)
I look like a young lady from the Joseon dynasty.
- You look so elegant.
- I look like a young lady.
Your hair looks like it was styled by a professional.
(Salon Director Roh is proud.)
(This guy looks like he was styled by a professional too.)
(Looking cool)
(Laughing)
- You really went all out.
- Why are you laughing?
You really dressed up.
- You're really dressed up.
- You told me to dress up.
(Captain Yum thinks it cute to see You Seok all dressed up.)
- Let's go.
- Let's go before they close.
- Okay.
(Let's make You Seok's dream of riding a luge together come true!)
As long as You Seok's happy.
Of course, that's why I'm even going.
Why are you so eager to ride it?
When else would I get the chance to come to Tongyeong...
with my older sisters, my older brother,
and my younger sister, and go luge riding together?
(If not now, when?)
- Goodness.
We only get this moment once.
He's much more articulate now.
What a smooth talker.
- The way he worded that.
- Let's live in the moment.
- Goodness. Carpe diem?
- Carpe diem.
(Listening to You Seok's smooth talking,)
We'll never have this moment again.
(they arrived at the luge track before they knew it.)
- Gosh.
- This looks amazing.
(As Korea's first luge attraction,)
(it offers thrilling speeds and panoramic views of the ocean.)
(As you glide down the 3.8km-long track,)
(following the pull of gravity,)
(the breathtaking waters of Tongyeong unfold before you.)
(It's one of Tongyeong's must-visit attractions.)
I'm dressed like a hunter today.
- What are you hunting?
- My older sisters' hearts.
Gosh.
Come on, You Seok.
- We got this.
- Come on, Jung Ah.
(The excitement brings out You Seok's even cuter side.)
- Hello.
(They're taking the lift up to the luge starting point first.)
- This isn't scary.
- Hello.
Hello.
- This scares me.
- She's scared to get on this one.
You Seok, I'm nervous.
I'll sit next to you and hold your hand.
Gosh.
- Goodness.
- I'll sit on the end.
Please sit down and lean your head back.
The bar will go down.
(Nervous)
- You can't ski, then?
- No.
You have to get on these when you go skiing.
I can't even ski because I'm too scared of getting off this.
So you like skiing.
(Off they go!)
Gosh, this is fun!
- This is fun, right?
- This is fun.
So that's how we go down.
(Gosh!)
(Jung Ah is startled by the sudden jolt.)
I'm okay.
I love this.
(Sweet You Seok holds Jung Ah's hand to comfort her.)
It was the wind.
This must be our track down there.
(Is now the time?)
That must be the track.
Gosh, look behind us. Turn around.
- Why would I do that?
- Wait.
Gosh.
(An incredible view unfolds behind the siblings.)
- This is it.
- This is great.
- The view behind us is amazing.
- I can see the ocean behind us.
- Gosh.
Amazing.
Gosh.
The view is incredible.
(A never-ending blessing of breathtaking views unfolds.)
- This is so nice.
- It's so pretty.
Every time we actually come and do the things you suggest,
we end up having such a great time.
I'm sure Sun Young and Jung Ah will end up loving it later too.
(They reached the top.)
(Run!)
The lift behind you isn't coming that fast.
- This is so fun.
- Gosh.
(They arrived at the starting point, surrounded by the stunning view.)
- This is going to be fun.
- Is this it? It's a one-man ride?
(Safety briefing and operating instructions before the ride)
Who wants to start first?
You Seok, if you want to go fast, go ahead.
Go live your dream.
Which why do I go? Left?
(KangRider is more than happy to.)
Let's do this!
Let's go.
(The siblings set off one by one.)
(Congratulations, You Seok! You got your wish!)
(The luges start to pick up speed.)
This is fun.
- The view is amazing.
- It is.
- The ocean looks incredible.
- It's great.
(The ocean view makes the luge ride even more refreshing.)
(Hae Joon, the last one to set off, is picking up speed too.)
(Peek-a-boo)
- It feels like we're overseas.
- Like we're in another country.
- There's no one else here.
- Right.
(While the rest of the siblings are enjoying the speed,)
(Sun Young is...)
This is so scary!
(Kim Sun Young: Rusty driver, has zero tolerance for speed)
Why are the brakes so heavy?
(On top of that, the brakes are too heavy for her.)
If I let go, it will go too fast. Gosh, I'm scared.
This is so scary.
(Caught between a rock and a hard place)
(Her friend, Hae Joon, has been watching her.)
Where's Sun Young?
(Where's Sun Young?)
She said she'd take it slow and not to worry about her.
(Instead of helping, he quickly ditched her.)
(Concerned)
(Worried about Sun Young, You Seok slows down.)
Are you okay?
Yes, you go ahead. I'm fine.
I'm just taking my time. Don't worry about me.
I'm okay. I'm just being safe.
I'll be down there.
(Feeling reassured,)
(You Seok quickly catches up to the leading group.)
I should let him pass.
(Yoon Seo, currently in the lead, feels the pressure.)
(You Seok takes the inside line with an aggressive strategy.)
Sir, I think you're a little too excited.
(He's flying!)
(This is so exciting!)
Just you wait. I'll catch up to you.
(After a close race between the two youngest siblings,)
Gosh, this is fun.
(they arrive at the finish point!)
That was so fun.
Yoo Seok, do you want to go again?
Hae Joon, you can go for another ride.
Yoon Seo, do you want to go again too?
Sun Young and I will wait here. You guys go ahead.
We older folks will wait down here.
You're not going for another ride? Come on.
All right, then. I will.
- You want to go fast, right?
- Yes.
- Yes?
- Let's ride together.
(Meanwhile, Sun Young...)
(finished the ride successfully.)
Gosh, she's here!
(Completely exhausted)
Goodness.
(Crying)
Gosh, it was so fun. The best.
- Jung Ah, it was truly...
- Those three went for another ride.
(Gosh)
I see. I wish I could ride again too.
(These three genuinely wanted to ride again.)
He's having a blast.
Look at him speeding down.
(You Seok finally lets loose and speeds down the track.)
Gosh, this is great.
(Hae Joon hums happily while cruising down the track.)
(They each enjoyed another ride on the luge in their own way.)
He's back.
(You Seok arrives first after racing to his heart's content.)
Was it fun?
Did you drive as fast as you could?
It was so much fun.
- Was it so much fun?
- It was so much fun.
If you had fun, that's all it matters.
- Seriously.
- Yes.
(Soon, Hae Joon and Yoon Seo also arrive.)
That was very...
(Exclaiming)
(Hae Joon's spectacular arrival performance)
What's wrong with him?
- You should hold her hand too.
- Okay.
(After taking commemorative photos on the podium)
One, two, three.
(The Tongyeong luge adventure is officially conquered.)
- Let's go eat.
- Let's go.
(After the end of the fun luge ride)
(To use the dining voucher they won yesterday,)
(they head to Tongyeong's famous Dajji Street.)
- Hello.
What a lucky day.
We got to ride the luge.
And now we get to enjoy Dajji too.
- We get to enjoy Dajji.
My goodness.
(A day filled with good fortune)
The name "Dajji" comes from the phrase "everything is there."
"Everything is there?"
It could be a Korean word.
- Everything is there.
Everything is there.
(Tongyeong's iconic Dajji is...)
(a feast featuring the freshest seafood caught the same day.)
(Everything is on the table.)
(That's the story behind the name "Dajji.")
The menu here is simple.
- It's 1 set per person.
- It's 45 dollars per person.
- Per person.
- One set per person.
(Order for the number of people, and we take care of the rest.)
- Dajji.
- Everything is there.
We have everything.
- Hello.
Hello.
(And now, the feast begins.)
Is it abalone porridge? What kind of porridge is it?
- This is abalone porridge.
- I see.
Bon appetit.
- What is it?
- It's seasoned sea squirt.
Oh, my.
(Seasoned sea squirt)
- Gosh.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
(Grilled tilefish and rosy seabass)
My goodness.
Raw anchovies?
- My gosh.
- It's raw anchovies.
- Raw anchovies?
- Anchovies.
(And a colourful raw anchovy salad)
More food is coming.
- Gosh, it's endless.
- Yes.
There's not enough space.
It's like a game of Tetris.
(Almost like playing Tetris)
There's a lot of food.
- Excuse me.
- Oh, my.
(It's too early to be shocked.)
(Steamed blue crab)
- This is murex.
- Murex?
It's a type of shellfish.
What should I start with?
(Boiled monkfish)
- Octopus?
- Yes.
- It's live octopus.
- Gosh.
It has all types of seafood in Tongyeong.
(And assorted seafood)
Where will you put that?
- What?
- Where could we possibly put it?
I should either hold it...
or take some out.
(There's not even enough space to put it.)
- Thank you.
- You're welcome. Enjoy it.
- Do you serve this much food?
- Yes.
- You always serve it like this?
- How much more...
- It depends...
on what's available at the market that day.
- Each day?
- The menu also depends...
on the weather.
Sea squirts are only available until June.
This is such a feast.
- Bon appetit.
- Thank you for the food.
This is amazing.
- The meal looks delicious.
- "The meal looks delicious?"
- It's "thank you for the meal."
- Oh, that's right.
There are so many that I don't know where to start.
I don't know where to start either.
- I really have no idea.
- Me neither.
(It's a happy dilemma.)
- This is octopus.
- This is fascinating.
It's fascinating.
(Humming)
(A taste that makes your eyes widen)
It's good.
Don't we just eat this?
- Of course.
- Have some rice.
- My gosh.
- We worked hard today.
- The raw fish is incredible.
- Eat a lot.
- Is the raw fish excellent?
- It's very fresh.
- Enjoy the food.
- Isn't the raw fish amazing?
- Yes.
Sea squirt.
- I'll eat it as much as I want.
- Because of work...
I know.
Do you eat on time?
(Pulling out the murex from the shell)
(Gobbling it up neatly)
Gosh, this is nice.
It seems like the middle-aged man showed up for a moment.
It happens sometimes.
(This is the seafood paradise, and Mr. Kang is in love with it.)
- It's baby octopus.
- Try it...
in a wrap.
- Isn't the baby octopus tasty?
- Yes.
How does it taste?
It tastes like squid.
- Does it taste like squid?
- Yes.
- Then it must be good.
- Sea squirt...
- Because of the eyes...
Right.
It has eyes. We made eye contact.
(Bright-eyed)
- You made eye contact?
- Yes.
Does it have a mouth?
- It has a mouth.
- You don't feel it?
I can feel all of them. The eyes, the nose, and the mouth.
My goodness.
(Your eyes, nose, mouth)
(Dancing)
(Eating out even makes Captain Yum dance.)
Now that everyone had a drink...
My goodness.
All right.
After the meal, everyone should get some rest.
Aren't you our guest?
You sound like the host.
(People might think that he's the host.)
(The younger ones are peeling the shrimp diligently.)
What do you think about the shrimp debate?
The shrimp debate? What about it?
What's the shrimp debate?
(The shrimp debate?)
- It's...
- It's like the perilla leaf debate.
- Right.
It's about peeling shrimp for your partner's friend...
of the opposite sex.
(If your partner peels shrimp for another person...)
(of the opposite sex, is that okay or not?)
- Right.
- Oh, my.
- You mean, my husband?
- Yes.
- For example...
- Why would he?
- Doesn't she have any fingers?
- My husband peels shrimp...
(Shaking)
- "Fingers?"
- My husband peels shrimp...
for another woman?
So...
Why would you peel that for her?
I didn't.
That's not okay.
Why would he do something like that?
That's totally unnecessary.
What do you think?
I don't really care.
If someone wants to do it, they can.
(What did you say?)
- If someone doesn't want to...
- Let's say your wife is...
sitting across the table a little far from you.
She starts peeling shrimp for a male friend...
- Your male friends.
- sitting in front of her.
- A man is peeling it?
- No, for a man.
It depends on who that man is.
He's very similar to you.
- He makes more money than you, - Goodness.
and he's more handsome than you.
It's someone you'd find impressive.
- Someone I'd feel jealous of?
- Yes.
- So what do you think?
- Gosh.
- You wouldn't be okay, right?
- I wouldn't be okay.
He shook his head about four times.
- That's not okay.
- It's not okay.
- Of course not.
More food is coming.
- More?
- Yes.
You brought it at the perfect time.
This is the last one this year.
Really?
- What is it?
- It'll be available next spring...
- when azaleas bloom.
- It's azaleas.
(Flower jeon made with azaleas)
- That's fascinating.
- Is it made with glutinous rice?
- Yes, it's glutinous rice.
- So that's why.
It looks very unusual.
- By the way...
- I've never had it before.
Jeon is often made with glutinous rice in Gyeongsang Province.
- It's like rice cakes.
- I agree.
(Everyone is savouring the azalea jeon together.)
- It's very unique.
- I love this.
It's my kind of style.
Gyeongsang Province style.
- Yes.
- It's like rice cakes.
- I haven't had this in a long time.
- Me neither.
- My mom used to make it for me.
- Exactly.
- Do you usually make this at home?
- Yes.
- At home, - I haven't tasted this...
- in a very long time.
- we made it this small.
We made it this small with a lot of oil.
This one is big, but my mom made it this small...
in several pieces.
- The taste of home.
- Are these azaleas?
Yes.
(Jeon made with his mother's love)
I see.
It's like hotteok.
- We eat it like this.
- It's so good.
(You find both flavours and memories at Dajji.)
Suddenly, there was a strong gust of wind.
The boat started rocking,
and the ladies in the back screamed.
How do you know? Did the captain tell you?
- He told me about it.
- Did he tell you?
Pretty ladies screamed and everything.
He's so silly.
(You Seok tells the story of the outboard boat.)
I want to go fishing.
What if we go fishing and catch something?
(Eyes closing tightly)
- I don't think it's a good idea.
- You're driving me crazy.
Jung Ah, I don't like it either.
- I keep making things bigger...
- It's a bad idea.
- than they need to be.
- This isn't it.
I'm afraid that Jung Ah will hate me.
So I'll stop taking on big projects.
What I want to do is very important.
Then you can go fishing alone.
- So...
- You can go...
I won't take you with me.
- I'm not going.
- I'll go fishing alone.
I'll make breakfast,
- so you and Hae Joon can go.
- We'll go and catch fish.
- We'll make breakfast.
- And we'll go fishing.
- Good luck.
- We'll make breakfast instead.
- I won't take you with me.
- Okay.
I feel more comfortable on the boat.
- Father.
- Gosh, spicy fish stew is served.
- Yes?
Three things tomorrow...
- Running, - Okay.
cycling, or a boat ride.
Which do you want to do the most?
Which is the best? Running is the easiest.
- Running?
- Yes, it's the easiest.
You don't want to go on a boat?
What would we do on a boat?
(It's a story we've heard before.)
He fell for it.
- He got caught.
- He'll end up on the boat anyway.
- Right. Whatever You Seok says...
- Jung Ah.
- comes true.
- He'll end up on the boat.
- Jung Ah.
- Whatever he says...
- comes true.
- We'll only look at the outcome.
Weren't you on a boat today?
But you weren't.
He's crazy about boats.
- But I'm scared of...
- I told you not to get on the boat!
(Suddenly, he turns into Yang Gwan Sik.)
- "I told you not to get on it."
- You're meant to ride the boat.
He was meant to?
- You kept trying to stop me.
- What did I tell you?
- You stopped him last time.
- I won't get on the boat.
You stopped him last time.
- Then let's do it.
- You can also operate it.
- It's very easy.
- No, I can't.
Be clear about it now. If you don't want to ride the boat,
we can go running.
What's there not to like when I'm doing it with you?
- That's right. He's your son.
- My gosh.
My gosh.
He's very moved right now.
I just looked at him from the side.
- He's truly moved.
- Doing something...
- with You Seok...
- He's really touched.
I looked at him briefly...
from the side.
He's really touched.
This is great.
He was stunned for about three seconds.
(Finally, it begins.)
(The siblings' curry battle)
(Mission! Satisfy Chef Yum!)
(Roh Yoon Seo, the brazen curry newbie)
(Kim Sun Young, the curry racer)
(Park Hae Joon, the curry expert)
(Kang You Seok, the detail king)
(It's like the curry special of "Culinary Class Wars.")
(There is a secret behind this curry.)
(Guys, help me!)
(In broad daylight,)
(a mysterious kidnapping incident takes place?)
(Forget the peace you've enjoyed so far!)
(They go back and forth between the kitchen and the field.)
(The siblings' culinary war is about to begin.)
(How will this story end?)
(The second story of the siblings, Taean, South Chungcheong Province)
(A bit of a shy guy makes his appearance.)
(I'd say my appearance is my main charm.)
(This guy is modest as well.)
(He makes the four siblings' hearts flutter.)
(Cho Jung Seok will be joining with the siblings.)
(I won't be able to fall asleep tonight.)